<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Q-Up</string>
    <string name="enter_facility_button">Enter Facility</string>
    <string name="retry_button">Retry</string>
    <string name="home_title">Home</string>
    <string name="app_welcome">Welcome to Q-Up</string>
    <string name="setu_button">Enter SETU</string>
    <string name="map_title">Attraction Map</string>
    <string name="permissions_title">App Permissions</string>
    <string name="back_button">Back</string>
    <string name="join_queue_button">Join Queue</string>
    <string name="leave_queue_button">Leave Queue</string>
    <string name="emerald_park_button">Enter Emerald Park</string>
    <string name="attraction_list_button">Attraction List</string>
    <string name="attraction_detail_button">Attraction Details</string>
    <string name="map_button">Facility Map</string>
    <string name="queues_button">Your Queues</string>
    <string name="loading">Loading...</string>
    <string name="loading_failed">Failed to load result. Check internet connection and try again. If issues persists, request assistance from facility staff.</string>
    <string name="attraction_name_label">Name</string>
    <string name="attraction_type_label">Type</string>
    <string name="attraction_status_label">Status</string>
    <string name="attraction_queue_time_label">Estimated Queue Time</string>
    <string name="attraction_queue_time_short_label">Est. Queue Time</string>
    <string name="attraction_queue_time_remaining_label">Remaining Queue Time</string>
    <string name="attraction_length_label">Length</string>
    <string name="attraction_max_cap_label">Max Capacity</string>
    <string name="attraction_length_unit">sec.</string>
    <string name="attraction_queue_time_unit">mins.</string>
    <string name="attraction_cost_label">Price</string>
    <string name="attraction_location_label">Location</string>
    <string name="attraction_description_label">Description</string>
    <string name="join_queue_success_alert_title">You\'re in!</string>
    <string name="leave_queue_confirmation_alert_title">Leave Queue?</string>
    <string name="leave_queue_confirmation_alert_desc_1">Are you sure you want to leave the queue for </string>
    <string name="leave_queue_confirmation_alert_desc_2">You will lose your queue position. </string>
    <string name="leave_queue_success_alert_title">Left Queue</string>
    <string name="no_queues_joined_desc">You are not queued for any attractions. Head over to the attraction list and join a queue.</string>
    <!--append attraction name to end-->
    <string name="join_queue_success_alert_desc">You have queued-up for </string>
    <string name="leave_queue_success_alert_desc">You have left the queue for </string>
    <string name="error_alert_title">Error</string>
    <string name="join_queue_error_409_alert_desc">You are already queued for this attraction.</string>
    <string name="error_500_alert_desc">Something went wrong. Check your internet connection and try again.</string>
    <string name="alert_okay">Okay</string>
    <string name="alert_confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="alert_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="alert_close">Close</string>
    <string name="expand_collapse_label">Expand/Collapse</string>
    <string name="attraction_in_queue_label">You are queued for this attraction</string>
    <string name="permissions_top">Q-Up requires the following permissions to enable full functionality:</string>
    <string name="permissions_notification_title">Notifications</string>
    <string name="permissions_notification_desc">Q-Up sends notifications with updates about queues and queue times.</string>
    <string name="permissions_Location_title">Location</string>
    <string name="permissions_Location_desc">Q-Up uses your location to calculate when to send you notifications to start moving towards an attraction. Both "Precise" and "Broad" location are permitted, but for best functionality, select "Precise". </string>
    <string name="permissions_camera_title">Camera</string>
    <string name="permissions_camera_desc">Q-Up needs to use the camera to scan your ticket. The camera is only used for scanning the ticket.</string>
    <string name="permissions_ask">Please press the button below and allow all permissions to continue to the application.</string>
    <string name="permissions_button">Check Permissions</string>
    <string name="permissions_denied">Permissions Denied</string>
    <string name="permissions_denied_desc">One or more app permissions were denied. These permissions are required for the app to function. Please go to the app settings and enable permissions for Notifications</string>
    <string name="open_settings_button">Open Settings</string>
    <string name="entrance_ticket_available">Entrance ticket available</string>
    <string name="entrance_ticket_expired">Entrance ticket expired</string>
    <string name="entrance_ticket_button">View Entrance Ticket</string>
    <string name="entrance_ticket_title">Entrance Ticket</string>
    <string name="camera_title">Scan Code</string>
    <string name="camera_top">Scan the QR Code provided by the facility at entry or as part of your ticket to continue.</string>
    <string name="generic_error">Something went wrong.</string>
    <string name="ticket_error_460">This ticket is not active yet. Confirm the entry time in your booking and request assistance from facility staff if required.</string>
    <string name="ticket_error_461">This ticket has expired. If you believe this to be an error, request assistance from facility staff.</string>
    <string name="ticket_error_462">This ticket has already been activated. If you believe this to be an error, request assistance from facility staff.</string>
    <string name="ticket_error_misc">Something went wrong. Exit this screen and try scanning your code again. If issues persist, request assistance from facility staff.</string>
    <string name="exit_facility_alert_title">Exit Facility?</string>
    <string name="exit_facility_alert_desc">Are you sure you want to exit the facility?</string>
    <string name="exit_facility_button">Exit Facility</string>
    <string name="exit_facility_and_reset_id_button">Exit Facility and Release User ID</string>
    <string name="entrance_ticket_top">This is your entrance ticket</string>
    <string name="entrance_ticket_desc">Present this ticket at the attraction entrance to gain entry.</string>
    <string name="entrance_ticket_important_info">Important Information</string>
    <string name="entrance_ticket_scan_info">Do not scan this ticket yourself. Doing so may cause you to lose your entrance ticket.</string>
    <string name="entrance_ticket_brightness_info">Ensure your screen brightness is sufficient for the QR code to be visible.</string>
    <string name="info_button">Info</string>
    <string name="map_info">This is the Attraction Map. The map below displays all the attractions in the facility. Your current location is displayed as a blue dot on the map. Tap a map marker to show the attraction name and status/queue time, then the info window that appears to go the attraction\'s details page.\n\nIf you are queued for an attraction, your remaining queue time will be displayed in the info window.\n\nTo get directions to an attraction, tap the marker, then press the blue arrow in the bottom right of the map. This will open the Google Maps app and show you directions to the attraction.</string>
    <string name="list_info">This is the Attraction List. A list of all the attractions in the facility is displayed, sorted alphabetically. Each entry in the list displays the attraction name, attraction type, and estimated queue time. If the attraction is not open, the attraction\'s current status is displayed instead.\n\nTap an attraction in the list to go to that attraction\'s details page.\n\nIf you are queued for an attraction, your remaining queue time will be displayed along with a message noting that you are queued for that attraction.</string>
    <string name="queues_info">This is Your Queues. All the attractions you are currently queued for are displayed below, with the estimated remaining queue time. Tap on a queue entry to expand it, and press the \"Attraction Details\" button to go to that attraction\'s details page, or press \"Leave Queue\" to leave the queue.\n\nWhen there are 5 minutes remaining in your queue, your Attraction Entrance Ticket will become available, denoted by a \"Entrance ticket available\" message on the queue entry. When displayed, opening the queue entry will show a third button, \"View Entrance Ticket\". Press this button to go to the entrance ticket for this attraction.\n\nAfter this entrance ticket is generated, you have 20 minutes to enter the attraction, or else your ticket expires and you lose your position in the queue. You will be sent a reminder notification periodically to enter the attraction.\n\nYou may receive a notification telling you to start heading to the attraction. This is sent based on your current location so can make it to the attraction by the time your entrance ticket is available.</string>
    <string name="attraction_info">This is the Attraction Details. All the details about the select attraction are displayed, including the name, type, total length, max capacity, price (if any), location, and description, along with an estimated queue time.\n\nIf the attraction is open, a \"Join Queue\" button will be available in the bottom left of the screen. Press this to join the attraction queue.\n\nIf you are already queued for the attraction, a \"Leave Queue\" button will be available in the bottom left of the screen. Press this to leave the attraction queue.\n\nTo get directions to the attraction, tap the marker, then press the blue arrow in the bottom right of the map. This will open the Google Maps app and show you directions to the attraction.</string>
    <string name="camera_info">Scan the entrance QR code provided as part of your facility entry or booking to use the application and join virtual queues. If you do not have an entrance QR code or are having issues scanning the code, request assistance from facility staff.</string>
</resources>